

0937-324-826 dumdumgenius@gmail.com Taiwan ,Taichung



### Introduce

Hello, I'm Yi Chung Yang, I come from Taiwan and graduated from Chiao Tung
University. I have quick thinking and good knowledge of mathematics and
physics, and for most important, I like coding. I got my bachelor degree of EE, but I chose to start my
career as a developer with on reason, I love it! Now I'm a full-stack developer for about two years. I used
Java, NodeJS, Ruby to build up back-end, while React.js and Angular.js in front-end. Also I can speak
English and some Japanese, I've been looking for a chance to work with people all over the world!

p.s: Must to see my website: http://www.dumdumgenius.com

## Experience

#### NATURALTEL - 2015 - 05 ~ 2016 - 04 ( JAVA ENGINNER )

Here're some important projects I was involved in.

#### **IVR System:**

It's a system which serves people when they call the number we provide. once the call connected, they will hear some voices that guide them to do some action like purchasing, querying account balance, change the default language and so on.

I finished this project with another partner, we use VXML language to deal with the logic of every action, while using Java to built up our APIs. It's first job of my career, it's tough in the start but it was interesting for me.

#### Warning System:

In this project, we collect every data that delivered by users and store them in our database. And about every hour, we will analyze this datas and see if there's any problem with them, once we find, the mail will be sent to person in charge.

I took charge in the most important part of this project, I write the data parser. In this parser I transfer the binary data to information and I do some magic that you can decide what kind of datas you want and where to store them by not changing the code but just configure file. I use some concept of Data Structure, so even the data is big, we can still finish the job in short time.

#### **SYNTRONTECH - 2016 - 04 - NOW ( JAVASCRIPT ENGINEER)**

In this company, I'm a full-stack engineer, and I built up a platform from ground zero with my partners.

#### Synhealth Platform:

It's a enterprise-face platform, it is built for Direct Selling use. We have many roles like enterprise, agent, dealer, health carer and customer. You can use this platform to add some products or add new dealer or agent under a enterprise or you can make a deal with new health carer. What things you can do are

decided by which role you are, so it's a little complicated platform. Also we have an APP for customers, so we still need to build some API for mobile usage.

I played the full stacker in here (actually we have four full stacker), so we arranged our jobs by features. As a new request came, we will tear it into parts and assess the time-cost of every part, finally send them to all members and start working. It's the best team I've ever seen, and I love it!

## Education

Chiao Tung University - Bachelor, 2009 - 09 ~ 2013 - 06

Studied at Electronic Engineering, good at mathematics and I can do quick thinking. I showed great power on coding contest on my department. And that was my first time falling in love with coding.



# **Techniques**

- 1. Nice Language Skill (English, TOEIC: 835), (Japanese, JLPT: N2)
- 2. 2 year Experience of Java, JavaScript, also their framework spring and express
- 3. Familiar with front-end framework like Angular, React, and tools like webpack, gulp
- 4. Knowledge about data structure, algorithm
- 5. Server-side rendering, SEO, 3rd-party API
- 6. Postgres database and NoSQL database like Mongo
- 7. Use git, and know the git flow
- 8. Understanding Linux and some usual command

## Side Project

#### **Dumdumgenius's blog:**

I built this website because I want to learn React JS, in this project, I've learned how to use webpack, how to program in ES6, what is Redux and how to run it with React, what is Server Side Rendering and what is PostCSS. It's not beautiful but you can still check my project on Github.

Front End: https://github.com/DumDumGeniuss/dumdumgenius-blog

Back End: https://github.com/DumDumGeniuss/dumdumgenius-blog-backend

## Reference

Github: https://github.com/DumDumGeniuss

identity-name

My Own build Website: <a href="http://www.dumdumgenius.com">http://www.dumdumgenius.com</a>